pakreel.com 2013-06-26

# Privacy Policy - Pakreel

**Personal Information**

* Non-Account Activity. You can watch videos on Pakreel.com without having a Pakreel.com Account. You can also contact us about a particular video without having a Pakreel.com Account.  
* Account-Related Activity. Certain other activities on Pakreel.com—like uploading videos, posting comments, flagging videos require you to have a Pakreel.com Account. We ask for some personal information when you create a Pakreel.com Account, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access.  
* Usage Information. We may record information about your usage, such as when you use Pakreel.com, the channels, groups, and favorites you subscribe to, the contacts you communicate with, the videos you watch, and the frequency and size of data transfers, as well as information you display or click on in Pakreel.com (including UI elements, settings, and other information). If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your account.   
* Content Uploaded to Site. Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your playback or profile pages, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.

**Uses**

* If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the Pakreel.com, we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the general and personalized features and functionality of the Pakreel.com, and to process any flagging activity or correspondence you send to us.  
* Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you upload videos or send messages through the Pakreel.com and other Users can contact you through messages and comments. Any videos that you submit to the Pakreel.com may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. If you have enabled Active Sharing, other users may see that you, as identified by your account name (not your email address), are watching the same video.  
* We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Pakreel.com Site changes or for customer service purposes).  
* We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the Pakreel.com and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, analyzing, and processing user preferences and trends, as well as user activity and communications.  
* We use cookies, and log file information to: (a) store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Pakreel.com; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests.

**Information That is Publicly Available**

* When you create an account on the site, some information about your account and your account activity will be provided to other Users of the site. This may include the date you opened your account, the date you last logged into your account, your age (if you choose to make it public), the country and the number of videos you have watched.  
* Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you engage in certain activity on the site, such as you upload videos or send messages through the Pakreel.com Site. Other Users can contact you through messages and comments.  
* You may also choose to add personal information that will visible to other Users on your channel page (which is the public facing page for your account on the site). This may include a profile picture, you name, gender, relationship status, or other details.  
* If you choose to add certain features to your channel page, then these features and your activity associated with these features will be displayed to other Users and may be aggregated and shared with your confirmed friends or other Users. Such shared activity may include what videos you favorite, what videos you rated and what videos you have uploaded.  
* Any videos that you submit to the Pakreel.com Site may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. If you have enabled Active Sharing, other users may see that you, as identified by your account name (not your email address), are watching the same video.

**Your Choices**

* You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the Pakreel.com, in which case you can still view videos and explore the Pakreel.com, but Pakreel.com may not be able to provide certain services to you.   
* You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting your account manager page.  
* You may clear your viewing history at any time through the "Viewing History" feature.  
* You may control the information that is available to other Users and your confirmed friends at any time by editing your account and the features that are included on your channel page.

**Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites  
**  
Pakreel.com allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Pakreel.com These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Pakreel.com. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.  
  Pakreel.com does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Pakreel.com to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 18-24 who have viewed certain channels of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the Pakreel.com, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks (i.e Adsense

™ , Adbrite™,  Axill™) for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. Pakreel.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. Any data obtained by third-party ad servers subsequently shared with Pakreel.com is maintained and dealt with by Pakreel.com in accordance with this privacy policy.

DoubleClick DART cookies  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [ http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx)

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.
